<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Association for Computing Machinery</title><link>https://tsuacm.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Association for Computing Machinery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tsuacm.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Main Street Kirksville Website</title><link>https://tsuacm.github.io/projects/mainstreet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tsuacm.github.io/projects/mainstreet/</guid><description>Main Street Kirksville is an organization whose mission is to strengthen historic Downtown Kirksville and promote it as an exciting place to shop, dine, live, work, be entertained, invest, and own a business.
WordPress based website Several custom WordPress plugins written Downtown Business Directory Business Promotion Slider Calendar Slider General Site Customizations Custom Post Types used to store business information Used CSS to heavily customize an existing WordPress theme Contributors Management Brandon Ingli Victor Wei Front End and Content Ashlyn Hanson Jagger Harris Sam Myers Thao Phung Slider Plugin Development My Vu Nestor Fong Lopez Katie Reeves Samuel Vaclavik</description></item><item><title>Final Meeting of Fall 2020</title><link>https://tsuacm.github.io/minutes/2020/11/16/final-meeting-of-fall-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tsuacm.github.io/minutes/2020/11/16/final-meeting-of-fall-2020/</guid><description>Notes from the Executive Board President &amp;ldquo;Have we got a show for you&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Vice President Python just beat out Java in the TIOBE Index Secretary Let Elena know if you aren&amp;rsquo;t receiving emails Minutes will be taken next semester! Recruitment Chair Join our slack if you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet Moving communication there from GroupMe Mentorship Chair Let Sam V know if you have ideas for new subgroups!</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tsuacm.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tsuacm.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hello, World! We are the Association for Computing Machinery, Truman State University Student Chapter!
Purpose To promote an increased knowledge of the science, design, development, construction, languages, and applications of modern computing machinery To promote a greater interest in computing machinery and its applications To provide a means of communication between persons having interest in computing machinery To provide an environment which fosters computer science education Contact Us Email: acm@truman.</description></item></channel></rss>